Guide to the Thomas S. Foley Photographs 1905-1995
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Thomas S. Foley Photographs
1905-1995
1964-1994
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
PC 111
Foley, Thomas S.
13 Linear feet of shelf space 13 Boxes
Collection consists of images of Thomas S. Foley including Family and political photographs, campaign and related material, and international photographs as part of his Congressional Papers.
Thomas S. Foley was born at Spokane, Washington, in 1929. He practiced law and worked for the Spokane County Prosecutor from 1957 to 1961, following his education at the University of Washington. From 1961 through 1964 he was on the staff of the Interior Committee of the United States Senate, a position he was introduced to by Senator Henry Jackson. In 1964, Foley won election as the Representative for Washington's Fifth District. Between then and 1994 he won fourteen more elections, ultimately serving in Congress for thirty years. He left Congress after the election of 1994, in which he was unsuccessful.
Foley became Chairman of the House Agriculture Committee in 1974, Majority Whip in 1981, Majority Leader in 1987 and Speaker of the House of Representatives in 1989. He also held other Democratic Party leadership posts in the party caucus and its Steering and Policy Committee. In 1997, he was appointed United States Ambassador to Japan.
This collecion consists of photographs of Thomas S. Foley, including personal family and political photographs, including campaign photographs and related material, as part of his Congressional Papers. Many include his wife, Heather Foley, as well as notable political figures, including Presidents and Foreign Dignitaries. Unless otherwise indicated Thomas S. Foley appears in every photograph in the collection. Individuals appearing in the photographs have been identified if possible.
The collection is roughly arranged into four series:
Family and Political Photographs; arranged chronologically.
Campaign Photographs and Related Material; arranged chronologically.
International Photographs; arranged alphabetically by country, and then chronologically.
Large Material; For better storage, larger materials were seperated out of their series and filed in seperate boxes at the end of the collection.
This collection is open and available for research use.
This collection of photographs was separated from the Thomas S. Foley Congressional Papers 1964-1997 (Cage 655) which were donated to the Washington State University Libraries in 1995. The photographs were accessioned as UPC-0003.
Thomas S. Foley Congressional Papers, 1964-1997 (Cage 655)
Kenton Bird Papers, 1950s-2003 (Cage 802)
Thomas S. Foley Papers, 1962-2001 (MSSM.073)
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Foley, Thomas S. -- Archives.; Foley, Thomas S. -- Photographs.; Foley, Heather -- Photographs.
Foley Family -- Photographs.
Legislators -- United States -- Photographs.; Washington (State) -- Politics and government -- 20th century -- Photographs.
Politics and Politicians; Political Campaigns; Washington (State); Photographs
- Family and Political Photographs
  - Foley's Grandfather at Railroad Depot, circa 1905 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - At 3 years old, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - President Harry S. Truman, circa 1946 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets, 1960's (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - At committee on official conduct, 1960's (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bell System Earth Station, 1964 November (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Senator Majority Leader Mike Mansfield, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Senator Scoop Jackson, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Senator Scoop Jackson (signed), circa 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Liberty Bell (Washington pass), Nez Perce War Memorial of 1877, circa 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Speaker and Mrs. McCormack, circa 1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chris Gallagher Party, circa 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alex Sherwood, Spokane Tribe, circa 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - President Lyndon B. Johnson, Shaking Hands, circa 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Manson Project, Chelan Division, Chief Joseph Dam, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 5th District photos, Washington, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Joe Davis, Washington State Labor Council, 1965 August 10-12 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Senator and Mrs. Lee Metcalf of Helena, Montana, 1965 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - President Lyndon B. Johnson, Bill Signing, 1965 July 22 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Seattle Times" with Senators Jackson and Magnuson, Representatives Adams, Hicks, and Meads, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Senator Magnuson at Democratic Convention in New York, circa 1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Savings and Loan League Legislative Conference, 1965 February 2 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Assistant Secretary of Agriculture, circa 1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Senator Ted Kennedy, circa 1966 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Attorney General Robert Kennedy, circa 1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Speaker Carl Albert, Heather Foley, circa 1966 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Young Sailor, circa 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Personal - Various People, circa 1966-1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Campaign, Western Washington, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Campaign, Pacific NW Bell, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - President Lyndon B. Johnson, Vice President Hubert Humphrey at Grand Coulee Dam, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - President Lyndon B. Johnson with Vice President Hubert Humphrey, 1966 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - North Cross Highway, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Cadets, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Colonel Nelson and New Air Force Recruits, 1967 April (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Postmasters, 1967 May (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Washington Public Power Supplies System, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Robert Kennedy Campaigning in Spokane, Washington, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Vice President Hubert Humphrey, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Wenatchee Valley College, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Walgreen and Twigg, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Sailors, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bill McGregor and Gene Moos, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Senator Jackson at Spokane Public Safety Building, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Wenatchee, Washington, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Tom and Heather Foley's Wedding, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bonneville Power Association, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Omak Stampede, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - "Ten for Ten" Reception, 1968 Summer (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - FBI Director J. Edgar Hoover, 1968 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Dedication of Bridgeport State Park, 1968 October (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - John Merkel, 1968 November (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Heather Foley on Florida trip, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Lake Chelan, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Grand Coulee Forebay Dams, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Jacques Cressard, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Hike with Staff?, Wenatchee, Washington, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Posthumous Awarding of Medal of Honor Ceremony for Sergeant Bruce Grandstaff with Grandstaff Family, President Richard Nixon, 1969 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Spokane City College, 1969 October (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - House Agriculture Committee with Forest Products People, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Republic, Washington Fair, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Kennewick, Washington Fair, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Skiing with Heather Foley, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Ken Webster, Senator Magnuson, Jim Bender, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Congressional Delegation, circa 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Hawaii and Thailand, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - State Legislators, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Valley Picnic, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee and Chairman Thomas Morgan, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Tedford, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Bob Timms and Ellis Armstrong, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Receiving and award, circa early 1970s (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Before Blackboard, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Grand Coulee Dam, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Heather Foley with an Elephant, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - On an Elephant, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Icicle Creek Hike (with Staff?), undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Telethon, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Udall and Culver, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Union Officials, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Speaker Carl Albert, circa 1971 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Fund Raising Banquet in Spokane, Washington, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Mae Mead, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Okanogan County Commissioners, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Gladys Morgan, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Don Brockett, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Jim McGolderick, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Marc Henninger, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Governor Andrus, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Schweitzer Awards with Senator Magnuson, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Senator Alan Cranston of California, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Gene Vicker, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Senator Magnuson, 1971 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Washington State House Delegation, circa 1972 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Ground Breaking Speakers McCormack, O'Neill, Albert, and Wright, circa 1972 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Heather Foley at a Party, circa 1972 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Senator Scoop Jackson, Miscellaneous Campaign Photos, circa 1972 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Representative Mike McCormack, circa 1972 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Betty Drumheller, circa 1972 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Senator George McGovern, circa 1972 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - John Hempleman, circa 1972 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Joe Haussler, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Girl Scouts, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Pasco, Washington, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Tom Pelly Party, Last Picture of Hale Boggs, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Senator Jackson in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Reception for Senator Scoop Jackson, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Democratic Convention, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - "The Wenatchee World" Miscellaneous Scenic Mountains, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Congressional Session with President Gerald Ford, circa 1973 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Trip to the Himalayas with Jim Hutchensen, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Capitol Hill, West Front Extension, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Pote Videt, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Reception for Mr. and Mrs. Patman, Texas Congressional Delegation, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Secretary of Agriculture Earl Butz, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Secretary of Agriculture Earl Butz - Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Independent Bakers, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - In "Seattle Times", 1973 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Overseas Trip Slides and Negatives, 1973 March (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Washington State Society Dinner, 1973 April (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - "Jolly Wedding", 1973 June (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Bill Signing Ceremony with President Gerald Ford, circa 1974 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Jerry Rees and Fred Mewhinney, circa 1974 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Spokane Expo, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Dr. J. Lein of Washington State Nursing Association, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Brad and Lynn Kay 1974, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Mrs. Hansen's Reception, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - E. Riddell Lage of Federal Farm Credit Board, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - David Brower of Friends of the Earth, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Democratic Study Group Party, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - President Gerald Ford, Representatives Meed and Dent, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Gladys Spellman, Democrat Congressional Nominee to5th District Maryland, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Washington State Potlatch Party and Dinner, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Telegraph Key (Dawson, Quinn, Taylor, Davis), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Spokane Chamber of Commerce, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Bruce McPhaden of Kaiser Aluminum, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Agriculture Committee, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - National Education Association Ronald Robinson, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Pacific Northwest Waterways Association, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Representatives Ullman and Perkins at Agriculture Committee, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - KWSU TV, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Harold Blaine, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Staff File of Bill First - Columbia Basin Project, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Milking Cows and Receiving Award, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Constructors, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Sagamore Farms with Heather Foley, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Father Goffrey, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Jim Pauly and Steve Robinson on Capitol Steps, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Mike Murray, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Representative Steve Symms, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Heather Foley at National Limestone Institute, Inc. Annual Convention, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - As Chairman of Agriculture Committee, 1975 January (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - D. Smith, 1975 January (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Representative Poage, 1975 February (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Representative Gary Brewn, 1975 February (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - "Money" Magazine, 1975 April (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - "US News and World Report" Magazine, 1975 April 28 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Heather Foley with President Gerald Ford and "Advent Review" Group, 1975 October (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Party with Senator Jackson, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Addressing Coalition for a Democratic Majority, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - President Jimmy Carter, Formal, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Speaker Carl Albert, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Representatives Brock Adams and Lloyd Meeds, Senator Magnuson, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Hydro-Foil, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Fundraiser, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Heather Foley with Sandy and Leslie at Grand Coulee Dam, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Senator Jack in Florida, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Democratic Convention in New York with President Jimmy Carter, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - In New York, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Speaker McCormack, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Representative Norm Dicxon of Washington, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Representative Phil Burton, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Representative Poage and Secretary Hardin, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Senator Scoop Jackson in Florida, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Lake Roosevelt and Colville Indian Reservation with Steve Pringle and Audrey, 1976 April (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Carl Albert Tree Planting Event, 1976 December (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - "Farmland News", Kansas City, MO, 1976 December 21 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - President Jimmy Carter, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - International Relations Committee Reception, circa 1977 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - President Jimmy Carter Peace Treaty Address to Congress, circa 1977 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Joint Session of 95th Congress Honoring Vice President Hubert Humphrey, circa 1977 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Representative Dante Fascell of Florida, circa 1977 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - "Florida Citrus Mutual" Publication, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - White House Signing of Panama Canal Treaty, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Casual Single Shots with Heather Foley, 1977 August (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Fairchild Air Force Base, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Ellen Clark "Maid of Cotton", 1977 (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Clay Beck, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Representative Bill Alexander of Arkansas, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - President Jimmy Carter and Tip O'Neill with Mat Engraving, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Representative and Mrs. McCormack, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Secretary of Agriculture Bob Berglund, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Farm Bill Conference, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - President Gerald Ford, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Vice President Mondale at Party, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - W.I.F.E., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - White House Leadership Meeting with President Jimmy Carter, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Young Democrats" Convention in Goldsboro, North Carolina, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dining at White House with President Jimmy Carter, Vice President Walter Mondale, Speaker Tip O'Neill, House Leadership, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Representative Len Funk, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Study Group Harriman Dinner, 1977 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Omak, Washington, 1977 July (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Vice President Walter Mondale (signed) at Clambake at Mondale's Home, 1977 October (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Addressing New Representatives on Rule Changes Proposals, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Speaker Tip O'Neill, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Budget Proposal Discussion and Press Conference, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Agriculture Secretary Bob Bergland at Reception, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - President Jimmy Carter at White House Bill Signing, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Religious Figure, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Giving Speech at Podium, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Vice President Walter Mondale, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - National Cable TV "Old Pictures" with Speaker Tip O'Neill, President Jimmy Carter, others, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chris Cummins and Steve Lemman, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "With the Horse" in Omak, Washington, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Columbian Basin Project and Grand Coulee Dam, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Michigan State University Commencement, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Senator Magnuson and Governor Ray in Spokane, Washington, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Senator Jackson at Spokane Interstate Fairgrounds, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - President Jimmy Carter, Seated, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - President Jimmy Carter, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Presidential Commisssion on World Hunger, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Agriculture Bob Bergland (signed), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Senator Magnuson in Washington State, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Franklin County Meeting, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Washington State Democratic Convention, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Duck Hunting in Washington State, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - White House Meeting with President Jimmy Carter, Speaker Tip O'Neill, etc., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Addressing the Farmers Agriculture Committee, 1978 January (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - President Jimmy Carter in Spokane, Washington, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Secretary of Agriculture Bob Bergland, 1978 July (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Agriculture Committee, 1978 August (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Forum on Regulation Telethon, 1978 September (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - National Rifle Association Salute, 1978 October 3 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Brock Adams, Lowry, Pritchard, and Dr. Jack Lien, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Heather Foley and Snow at White House Greeting Pope John Paul, II, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Agriculture Committee Reception, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - State of Union Address 96th Congress, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Secretary of Interior Cecil Andrus, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - President Jimmy Carter, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Wheat Forum in Dayton, Washington, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Yancey Martin and Others, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Interview Outside Capitol, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - American Legion National Commander Frank Hamilton, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - March of Dimes Poster Child, Jim Wright, Speaker Tip O'Neill, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - "Outstanding Tree Farmers of America" with President Jimmy Carter, O'Connel, Mr. and Mrs. Albert Deishl, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - White House Meeting with President Jimmy Carter, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - White House Lunch with President Jimmy Carter, Speaker Tip O'Neill, etc., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - White House Meeting with President Jimmy Carter, Tip O'Neill, Jim Wright, etc., 1979 January 23 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Contact sheet and negatives of reception, 1979 February (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - White House Signing of Peace Treaty-Israel and Egypt, 1979 March (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Pasco, Washington Town Hall Meeting, 1979 April (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - World Food Policy Seminar, Harvard University, 1979 May 14 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Negatives - Grame Outer Bridge, 1979 June (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Camp David with President Jimmy Carter, 1979 June (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Tree Farmers Award Ceremony, 1979 September (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Meeting with House Conferees and Tip O'Neill, 1979 September 9 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Air Force Association Annual Salute to Congress, 1979 September 18 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Heather Foley with President Jimmy Carter and Mrs. Carter, 1979 October 9 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Dedication of Poage Library, 1979 November (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Bob Hope, circa 1980 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Heather Foley in "the Gallery", circa 1980 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Senators Magnuson, Jackson, and Dixie, circa 1980 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Marybeth Schultheis and George Kundanis, circa 1980 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Heather Foley Sitting at a Desk, circa 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - District Visit, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Miss Kona Coffee, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Leadership Breakfast at White House with President Jimmy Carter, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Color Slides of 5th District, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Speaker Tip O'Neill, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - President Jimmy Carter, Senator Talmadge, Secretary Bergland, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - World and Food Agricultural Outlook Members, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Agricultural Committee Reception, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Sewer Summit with Ron Bair, W. Mangnuson, H. Jackson, circa 1980 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Constituents, circa 1980 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - House Leadership and Sophia Loren, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Speaker Jim Wright's Portrait, circa 1980s (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Mikhail Gorbechev and Soviet Leaders, circa 1980s (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Heather Foley and Angie Dickenson, circa 1980s (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Color Slides - Constituents and Campaign Yard Signs, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Color slides - Ritzville, Tri-Cities, Pasco Bridge, Pres. Podium, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Slides - Irrigation Fields, Vinyards, and Union Building, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - President Jimmy Carter on Air Force One, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Democratic National Convention in New York, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Commodity Exchange, Inc. Visit, 1980 March (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Lamb-Western Plant in Cornell, Washington, 1980 April (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Gonzaga University with Tip O'Neill, F. Coughlin, Luke Williams, 1980 May (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - St. Paul's Dedication, 1980 May 18 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Mt. St. Helens, USDA, 1980 May 24 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Mt. St. Helens Eruption Satellite Photos, 1980 May 18-19 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Surveying Mt. St. Helens Ashes in 5th District, 1980 May (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Newphew Dick, 1980 Summer (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Carol Evavold of Gonzaga University, Heather Foley, and Dog, Alice, 1980 June (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Professor Williams of Nuffield College, Oxford University, 1980 September 23 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Representative McCormack Award Ceremony, 1980 September 26 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Agriculture Committee Reception for Secretary Bergland, 1980 November (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Speaker's Party, 1980 December (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Speaker's Party for Freshmen Members, 1980 December (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Jim Wright at New Members Dinner, 1980 December 5 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Participating in local parade with Judge Foley, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 103)